homebrewtalk.com 2016-05-29

# 

Cultured Media has created this privacy statement to demonstrate our firm commitment to the privacy of the users of our websites. We know that our users take their privacy seriously, and so do we. Please read the following to learn more about what information we collect and how we use it. By using our websites, you consent to this Policy. 

**What this Privacy Policy Covers**

This Policy covers Cultured Media's treatment of personally identifiable information collected by Cultured Media through websites owned and operated by Cultured Media. This Policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Cultured Media does not own or control, or of persons that Cultured Media does not employ or manage, including any third-party content contributors bound by contract and any third-party websites to which Cultured Media's websites link. This Policy only applies to information collected through our websites, and not to information collected offline. 

**What Information Does Cultured Media Collect?**

**1\. Personal Information**

You can visit Cultured Media's websites without revealing any personal information. However, Cultured Media needs certain personal information if you wish to register for a member account, receive a Cultured Media newsletter, or use certain Cultured Media services.

Where required, this information may include your company contact information and your personal contact information. Cultured Media uses this information to reply to your inquiries, to set up your member account, to provide you with requested services, and to contact you regarding new services.

By accessing the services of Cultured Media and voluntarily providing us with the requested personal information, you consent to the collection and use of the information in accordance with this Policy. 

**2\. Non-Personal Information**

Cultured Media automatically receives and records non-personal information on our server logs from your browser, including but not limited to your IP address, cookie information, and the page you requested. Cultured Media may use this information to customize the advertising and content you see and to fulfill your requests for certain products and services.

Cultured Media uses third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our websites. These companies may use information about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

Cultured Media uses cookies to keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about website traffic and website interaction in order to offer better site experiences and services in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to help us to better understand our websites' visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected except to help us provide and improve our services.

If you prefer, you may choose to have your computer warn you when a cookie is being sent, or you may choose to disable cookies through your browser's settings. However, as with most websites, some of Cultured Media's services may not function properly when cookies are disabled.

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

Cultured Media may disclose your personal information to third parties who work on behalf of Cultured Media to provide services to you. Cultured Media may also disclose your personal information when: We have your express consent to share the information for a specified purpose;

We need to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process or official request

We need to protect the personal safety of the users of our websites or defend the rights or property of Cultured Media; or

We find that your actions on our websites violate the Cultured Media Terms of Service Agreement or any of our usage guidelines for specific products or services

Your personal information may be shared with or sold to any successor to or purchaser of part or all of the assets of Cultured Media, or if Cultured Media is merged in whole or in part with another company. 

**Consent**

If you do not consent to the collection, use, or disclosure of your personal information as outlined in this Policy, please do not provide any personal information to Cultured Media. 

**How to Access Your Personal Information**

Cultured Media gives you the ability to edit your Cultured Media Account Information and preferences at any time, unless you have been banned. If you have been banned, we can, upon request, alter personal information limited to signature, email address, user name, and location. 

**Security**

Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be considered 100% secure. 

Should you believe your personal safety is threatened or that you may be the victim of identity theft or other illegal conduct, please contact your local, state/provincial, or federal law enforcement agencies directly. 

**Changes to This Privacy Policy**

Cultured Media, at its sole discretion, may, at any time and without notice amend this Policy. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below. 

**Questions or Suggestions**

If you have questions or suggestions about this Privacy Policy or your personal information, please contact us. 

This policy was last modified on November 22, 2011
